<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Columbia Psychology: Prospective Student Days</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Columbia Psychology: Prospective Student Days</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pets and Mascots</title>
      <link>/pets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pets/</guid>
      <description>  Pets and Mascots          </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/</guid>
      <description>Resources During Prospective Student Days, we will use a few different platforms to facilitate your virtual visit:
Kumospace  Kumospace is an immersive video chat platform that allows people to mingle within a virtual event space. During Prospective Student Days, our social events will take place on Kumospace at this link.
After logging in, you can move about the virtual room using your computer’s arrow keys. You will be able to hear the people close to you in the virtual space, and as you move away from them, their audio will fade out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/schedule/</guid>
      <description>Schedule Wednesday, February 17th   6:00p onward   Welcome Social
(Prospective and Current
Graduate Students)   Kumospace      Thursday, February 18th   10:00a - 10:30a   Information Session   Zoom     10:30a - 11:00a   Break       11:00a - 11:40a   Faculty Meeting 1   Zoom (see email)     11:45a - 12:25p   Faculty Meeting 2   Zoom (see email)     12:30p - 1:10p   Break (Lunch)       1:15p - 2:25p   Faculty Meeting 3   Zoom (see email)     2:30p - 3:10p   Faculty Meeting 4   Zoom (see email)      Friday, February 19th   10:00a - 11:00a   Lab Meetings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Tour</title>
      <link>/tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tour/</guid>
      <description>Virtual Tour Campus Although Columbia University was established in 1754, it moved throughout New York City several times before settling in its current location in 1897. Schermerhorn Hall, the location of the psychology department, is one of the original buildings in this current location. To learn more, check out the following virtual tour!
   Morningside Heights Columbia is located in the Morningside Heights, which is nestled between the Upper West Side and Harlem in the borough of Manhattan.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>