<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Columbia Psychology: Prospective Visit Days</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Columbia Psychology: Prospective Visit Days</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pets and Mascots</title>
      <link>/pets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pets/</guid>
      <description> Pets and Mascots                               </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/</guid>
      <description>Resources During Prospective Visit Days, we will use a few different platforms to facilitate your virtual visit. If you have any questions about how to use them, or if you experience any unforeseen technical difficulties, please don’t hesitate to let us know!
Kumospace  Kumospace is an immersive video chat platform that allows people to mingle within a virtual event space. During Prospective Visit Days, social events will take place at the event-specific Kumospace links found on the Schedule page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/schedule/</guid>
      <description>Schedule Wednesday, February 17th   6:00p onward   Virtual Social Event
Prospective and current graduate students   Kumospace      Thursday, February 18th   10:00a - 10:30a   Welcome
Dr. Kevin Ochsner, Department Chair [Faculty Profile]   Zoom     10:30a - 10:40a   Break       10:40a - 11:20a   Faculty Meeting 1   Zoom (see email)     11:25a - 12:05p   Faculty Meeting 2   Zoom (see email)     12:05p - 1:00p   Break (Lunch)       1:00p - 1:40p   Faculty Meeting 3   Zoom (see email)     1:45p - 2:25p   Faculty Meeting 4   Zoom (see email)     2:25p - 3:00p   Break       3:00p - 3:30p   Information Session</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Tour</title>
      <link>/tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tour/</guid>
      <description>Virtual Tour Campus Although Columbia University was established in 1754, it moved throughout New York City several times before settling in its current location in 1897. Schermerhorn Hall, the location of the psychology department, is one of the original buildings in this current location. To learn more, check out the following virtual tour!
Other useful resources: Columbia’s Official Virtual Tour Website
   Morningside Heights Columbia is located in the Morningside Heights, which is nestled between the Upper West Side and Harlem in the borough of Manhattan.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
